<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Marion</title>
 <link href="http://www.heymarion.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.heymarion.me/"/>
 <updated>2015-02-26T10:55:35-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.heymarion.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Marion Xu</name>
   <email>marion@heymarion.me</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Spring Break & AIESEC</title>
   <link href="http://www.heymarion.me/2015/02/26/spring-break-and-aiesec/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.heymarion.me/2015/02/26/spring-break-and-aiesec</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;So... spring break is tomorrow. I&amp;#39;m going home (Los Angeles!), and I&amp;#39;m super excited to get away from the snow. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On another note, I joined a student organization called AIESEC this semester. Well, it&amp;#39;s actually a student-run NGO. But I&amp;#39;ve been having pretty mixed feelings about it so far. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of AIESEC is to create leadership opportunities through exchange, i.e. it is an international volunteer/internship abroad program. I&amp;#39;m having a lot of trouble with the way the organization is run - everything is focused on numbers and quantity, which doesn&amp;#39;t really settle well with me. I was at a workshop this past weekend and I was told about how to deal with issues that may arise with exchange participants, some of which were not being able to do the work that was advertised, or even not having secure living conditions abroad. Why are these even problems? We should be vetting the organizations we partner with, and making sure that they will provide quality opportunities to participants, rather than simply focusing on the numbers game and trying to recruit as many traineeships (TNs) as possible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, there&amp;#39;s been a huge push for marketing in my chapter. I don&amp;#39;t know how to feel about this - I hate marketing, which is why I didn&amp;#39;t join the marketing function. But again, this is based on numbers - how many times you like a facebook post, how many information sessions you attend, etc. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, it isn&amp;#39;t all bad. I love the people in AIESEC and they&amp;#39;ve been a great support network. A lot of the people in AIESEC have basically dedicated their lives to the organization, which I definitely admire. However, I&amp;#39;ve noticed a lot of people in the organization want to travel abroad with AIESEC or feature it prominently on their resume - two things that I am not interested in at all. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hey There</title>
   <link href="http://www.heymarion.me/2015/02/18/hey-there/"/>
   <updated>2015-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.heymarion.me/2015/02/18/hey-there</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;#39;m Marion. I just created this website as a place for me to just write down random things and thoughts and ideas. I&amp;#39;m really not too sure what I&amp;#39;m going to do with this. It was a lot of fun to set up the template and layout and everything. I&amp;#39;m not really too sure. For now, here&amp;#39;s an empowering quote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;message&quot;&gt; 
    “I think it&#39;s much more interesting to live not knowing than to have answers which might be wrong. I have approximate answers and possible beliefs and different degrees of uncertainty about different things, but I am not absolutely sure of anything and there are many things I don&#39;t know anything about, such as whether it means anything to ask why we&#39;re here. I don&#39;t have to know an answer. I don&#39;t feel frightened not knowing things, by being lost in a mysterious universe without any purpose, which is the way it really is as far as I can tell.” &lt;br /&gt; -- Richard Feynman
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
